A Guide to the David Rockefeller Personal and Professional papers, Memoirs, RG 7 FA790
Rockefeller Archive Center
David Rockefeller Personal and Professional papers, Memoirs, RG 7
1906-2004
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
FA790
41.9 Cubic Feet 103 letter document boxes, 3 legal document boxes, 7 microfilm reels (16mm) and 1 record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of materials used and created in the prepartion of David Rockefeller's Memoris, including books of clippings from newspapers and periodicals that document the interests and activities of David Rockefeller through the 1980s, including his retirement from Chase Manhattan Bank in 1980.
The collection also includes research materials such as chronologies of David Rockefeller's activities and pertinent events, project ideas and chapter drafts, summaries of philanthropic activites and donations, political contributions, correspondence and transcripts of interviews with David Rockefeller and significant contemporaries, as well as documentation of preprations for book tour appearances accompanying release of Memoirs.
There is also a small selection of biographical materials, including correspondence with Peggy Rockefeller, correspondence with his parents John D. Rockefeller Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, documentation of educational activities including David Rockefeller's childhood experience at the Lincoln School, and his education at Harvard University and the London School of Economics.
Arrangement
Original order, as received. Materials are arranged in three series. Series 1: Clipping Books, Microfilm. Series 2: Clipping Books, Papers. Series 3: Research.
- Clipping Books, Microfilm, 1937-1981; 1; 0.06 Cubic Feet 7 16mm microfilm boxes.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  The microfilm was created by the staff of Room 5600, the Rockefeller family office at Rockefeller Center, and transferred to the Rockefeller Archive Center in the early 1980s.
  - Clipping Books, 1937-1942, 1959 (Reel 1)
  - Clipping Books, 1960-1966 (Reel 2)
  - Clipping Books, 1967-1971 June (Reel 3)
  - Clipping Books, 1971 July-1974 December (Reel 4)
  - Clipping Books, 1975-1978 September (Reel 5)
  - Clipping Books, 1978 October-1980 October (Reel 6)
  - Clipping Books, 1980 November-1981 April (Reel 7)
- Clipping Books, Paper, 1915-1989; 1951-1989; 2; 20 Cubic Feet 48 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box and 1 record storage box.
  Scope and Contents
  Cliiping Books primarily consist of newspaper articles, magazines and other periodicals. Many of the clipping books also contain materials consistent with traditional scrapbooks such as photographs, snapshots, programs, event announcements, awards, dinners, luncheons, and attendees lists. This series also contains a small set of Rockefeller family photograph albums and scrapbooks owned by David and Peggy Rockefeller.
  - Background Information on Organizations (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clipping Books, 1915; 1937-1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Clipping Books, 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Clipping Books, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Clipping Books, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 2-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 1-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1-5)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Clipping Books, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 1-6)
  - Clipping Books, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1-6, Box 21, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 1-4, Box 28, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1-4, Box 30, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1979-1980 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Clipping Books, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 1-5, Box 33)
  - Clipping Books, 1980-1982 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
  - Clipping Books, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1-5, Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Clipping Books, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1985 (Box 41, Folder 1-5, Box 42)
  - Clipping Books - Americas Society Trip, 1986 January (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Clipping Books, 1986 January-March (Box 48, Folder 4, Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Clipping Books, 1986 April-May (Box 49, Folder 2-3)
  - Clipping Books - Trilateral Commission, Madrid Plenary, 1986 May (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Clipping Books, 1986 June-December (Box 50, Folder 2-4)
  - Clipping Books, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1-4, Box 44, Folder 1-2)
  - Clipping Books, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 1-5)
  - Clipping Books, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 1-6)
  - Scrapbooks, 1915-1948 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Family Portraits and Snapshots (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Currency Album, 1940s (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbooks - Europe, 1935-1936 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks - Childhood (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
  - David Rockefeller and Family Portraits, 1915-1960 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - David and Peggy Rockefeller Wedding Album, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller and Family Portraits - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Research, 1906-2004; 3; 21.83 Cubic Feet 55 letter document boxes and 2 legal document boxes.
  - David Rockefeller Former Affiliations, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Affiliations, 1965 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fragmentary History of Rockefeller Center (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cousins Nominating Committee, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2031
  - David Rockefeller and the Soviet Union (USSR), 1960-1984 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - Commission on Money and Credit (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1946-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - William Waters Diary - Copy, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - America and Western Europe After World War II, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Center Study, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Richard Rockefeller Notes - Trip with DR to Europe and Middle East, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Negotiations with National Trust related to Pocantico, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1926-1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology - Harvard Years 1932-1936 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology - Postgraduate Years 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1968-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1950-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Meetings - Minutes, 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Meetings - Minutes, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Annual Review of Organizations, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Trip to the Far East, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Brothers Memoranda, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Pocantico Recommendations, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Appointment Books, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Appointment Books, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Appointment Books, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Books, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 1-3, Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Desk Calendar, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Desk Calendars, 1980, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3-4)
  - Appointment Books, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2-3)
  - Desk Calendars, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
  - Appointment Books, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
  - Desk Calendar, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Desk Calendars, 1995-1996 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Appointment Books, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2-6)
  - Appointment Books, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Address Book, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Pocket Diaries, 1947; 1958-1968 (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
  - Pocket Diaries, 1969-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1-4)
  - Pocket Diaries, 1985-1986; 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Pocket Diaries, 1993, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Trips to China, 1973-1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Interview with Gorbachev, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Center - History, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Center - Caneel Bay Meeting, 1985-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Banking Legislation, 1956-1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Memoirs Miscellany, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pocantico Discussions, 1980s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller Center - Goldman Sachs Offering Materials, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    Restricted - Open in 2027
  - Rockefeller Center and the 1934 Trusts (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Chase Valuation of Rockefeller Group Inc. (RGI), 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Restricted - Open in 2042
  - Rockefeller Center - A Masterpiece Evolving from a Family Commitment, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Center - The Rockefeller Group - 1984 Financial Statements (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. (RCI) - Long Range Strategic Plan, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Center, Inc. (RCI) - Financial Outlook for the 1980s (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Shearson Lehman Hutton - Strategic Alternatives - Rockefeller Group, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Management Files (Articles) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Latin American Articles (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Bohemian Grove, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Aunt Lucy Aldrich, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - French Restorations, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland History, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1930 Western Trip (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 1930 Western Trip - Art (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - State Park at Rockwood Hall - Environmental Impact Analysis, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Trips to Middle East and Asia (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Trips to Turkey, 1959, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Trips to India, 1963, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Egypt, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Israel, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Jordan, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Morocco Trips, 1970s-1980s (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Oman, 1970s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Trips to Pakistan (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1950s-1980s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Excursion to Southern Africa, 1995 September 10 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - South Africa (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Sudan, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 1984 Middle East Trip (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Middle East Names (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - New York City Housing Partnership (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Development Assistance - ODC (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1969 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller Center, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Assistance (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Russia/Ruble (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Acadia National Park, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Harvard, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Assistance - General Ideas, 1940-1990 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Rockefeller University (RU) - Mabel Bright, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Pocantico, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Assistance - Peterson Commission, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Center - Background, 1980-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Interview with Thomas LaBrecque - Peter Johnson and Joe Nolan, 1989 July 31 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Interview with David Rockefeller - Peter Johnson - Joe Nolan, 1989 June 2 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Interview with David Rockefeller - Peter Johnson - Joe Nolan, 1989 October 10 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Interview with David Rockefeller, 1989 July 18 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology - World War II, 1942-1945 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Brothers Meetings, 1964-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Business Commission on Jamaica - History (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Trilateral Commission Study, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1968-1981 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - David Rockefeller Trip List, 1929-1984 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Papers presented at JDR 150th Anniversary Conference, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Proposal for an International Institute of Science and Technology in International Affairs, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF) - Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund (RBF) - Special Meeting, 1978 October 5 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Grad Year - Schumpeter, 1974-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association (DLMA) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - New York City Material (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chile - Economic History, 1970s (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology 1926-1936 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Middle East - David Rockefeller Trips, 1959-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Suez Crisis 1956-1967, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller's 1984 Summary of Middle East (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 1974 Trip (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Business in New York - 19th Century (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Middle East - Iraq, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Middle East - Egypt, 1962-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Middle East - Egypt - Sadat, 1978-1992 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Middle East - Algeria, 1954-1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Arab Boycott, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Visits to Middle East, 1950-1992 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lebanon, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - China, 1973-1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Dartmouth Conference - History (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Winston Garth - 1932 Trip with David Rockefeller (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Brothers Meetings, 1962-1970 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Brothers Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - David Rockefeller Interviews - Warren Lindquist (Lindy), 1984 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - David Rockefeller - Taped Conversations, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1969-1984 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Oman, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Morocco, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Kuwait - History, 1917-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, 1974-1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - David Rockefeller Chronology and News Articles 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Chase Philanthropy - RB (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - New York City and Standard Oil in Russia (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - David Rockefeller's Early Urban Involvement - Draft (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Barnard Collection, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Cloisters and Barnard Collection, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - US Senate Seat - Charles Goodell, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller Center - Finances, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Housing - Thomas Garden Apartments, 1925 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - PLD Housing, 1935-1938 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - David Rockefeller Gifts to Harvard, 1941-1981 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Bawer Report Chase, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Iranian Crisis, 1981-1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Center (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pocantico and the Rockefeller Brothers, 1970-1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - China, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Chase - Annual Reports, 1960s-1970s (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Dartmouth Conferences, 1964-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Alliance for Progress, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Business Group of Latin America (BGLA), 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
  - Latin America - Alliance for Progress, 1970-1991 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Alliance for Progress, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Chase-Chemical Merger, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1981-2000 (Box 24, Folder 11A)
  - Memoirs Outline, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Fazenda Bodaquena - NAR, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Latin American Chapter - Bergsten Comments, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - The Shah of Iran, 1962-1981 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Center - Stock and Trusts (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Center - Historical Background (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - PRC - China (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 12 - XC - China (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - China Trips, Late 1970s-1980s (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Iran - Research on the Shah and Chase (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Endowment - Alger Hiss, 1947-1994 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Nelson Rockefeller, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Theremin, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Middle East - Iran, 1962-1999 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Shah - Iran, 1964-1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Iran - Hostage Crisis, 1979-1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Iran - Shah Material, 1962-1999 (Box 26, Folder 1-2)
  - Chapter 26 - New York, New York Research, 1990s (Box 26, Folder 3-4)
  - Articles on Housing and New York City (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Community Preservation Corp, 1990s (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Articles on JDR and JDR Jr. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Middle East - Memos and Documents, 1960-1985 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Boycott of Chase, 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Anti-Defamation League, 1970-1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Council on Foreign Relations and Trilateral, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Right and Left Wing Critics (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 17 - The Bad Year (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 18 - The Shah and Chase (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Iranian Investment Conference, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Pocantico - National Trust for Historic Preservation (NTHP) Plan, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - New York Times - Financial Crisis, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Institute of International Education (IIE) Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Americas Society Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Chase Archives - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association (D-LMA) Plans, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Chase Archives - David Rockefeller-Robert Moses Correspondence, 1955-1963 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Chase Archives - Downtown-Lower Manhattan Association (D-LMA) Material, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Chase Archives - Civic - National Urban Coalition (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Chase Archives - RBF - National Urban Coalition, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Manhattan Waterfront Plan, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Westway - News Articles, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Chase Archives - Gerald Ford and Arthur Levitt, Jr., 1960-1998 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Chase Archives - Mario Cuomo, 1974-1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Chase Archives - Summary Report of Business-Labor Working Group (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Chase - Annual Reports and Proxy Statements, 1960-1980 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - New York Times - 1967 - Urban Coalition (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 15 - MOMA and Our Collection, 1930-2000 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Articles on David Rockefeller and Family (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Michael Rockefeller Wing - MMA, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 16 - "Preface", 1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs Article on the Shah, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - David Rockefeller Clipping File Digest, 1978-1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Chronology, 1962; 1968-1982; 1984 (Box 29, Folder 2-3)
  - Chronology - Trips, 1929-1992 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Chronology - World War II 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Lydia Bodman (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Diego Rivera - Destruction of the Mural, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - World Leaders Declaration on Population, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller Center Articles, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Rockwood Hall - History (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - JDR - Historical, 1930s-1940s (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln School (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Memoirs - Economics (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Center (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Hugh McCauley, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Ron Chernow, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Peter Johnson - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Paul Growald - State Department, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - JDR Sr. and JDR Jr. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - LSR Studies, 1946-1955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - JDR 3rd - Finances, 1906-1933 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Americas Society - History - David Rockefeller Revisions, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Asia Society - Minutes, 1951-1977 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Federal Budget Information - Historical, 1940-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 26 - New York, New York (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 27 - Proud Internationalist, 1999 September 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 28 - South of the Border, 1999 September 1 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Chapter 29 - A Passion for Modern Art (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 30 - Rockefeller Center Redux, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 30 - The Rockefeller Family Incorporated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 31 - Epilogue, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 1 - Grandfather (Test 1) (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 2 - Mother and Father (Test 2) (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 3 - Childhood (Test 3) (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 4 - Family Trips (Test 4) (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 5 - Rockefeller Center (Test 5) (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 6 - Harvard (Test 6) (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 7 - Studying Economics (Test 7) (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 8 - A Dissertation, A Wife, and a Job (Test 8) (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 9 - The War (Test 9) (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 10 - Embarking on a Career at Chase (Test 10) (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 11 - Launching a Parallel Career (Test 11) (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 12 - Building the Chase Manhattan Bank (Test 12) (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 13 - Conflict (Test 13) (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 14 - Difficult Transitions (Test 14) (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 15 - Building a Global Bank (Test 15) (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 16 - Taking the Helm (Test 16) (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 17 - Engaging the Soviets (Test 17) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 18 - Penetrating the Bamboo Curtain (Test 18) (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 19 - The Middle East - Searching for Balance (Test 19) (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 20 - The Middle East - Surviving OPEC (Test 20) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 21 - Business Turbulence (Test 21) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 22 - Family Turmoil (Test 22) (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 23 - Brotherly Conflicts (Test 23) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 24 - The Shah (Test 24) (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 25 - Redemption (Test 25) (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 26 - New York, New York (Test 26) (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 27 - Proud Internationalist (Test 27) (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 28 - South of the Border (Test 28) (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 29 - A Passion for Modern Art (Test 29) (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 30 - The Rockefeller Family Incorporated (Test 30) (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Unabridged Memoirs - Chapter 31 - Epilogue - Partnerships (Test 31) (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Memoirs (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - DR Memoirs - Correspondence, Memos, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Chapters to be sent over to Andrew Wylie to be brought to Frankfurt, 1994-1999 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Memoirs Files - Newspaper Articles - Fortune, 1969-1977 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 34 - Down on the Farm, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 23)